{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "According to cliche, here are some things you just shouldn't do.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "cover",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't judge a book by its _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "feeds you",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't bite the hand that _____ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "hatch",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't count your chickens before they _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "parade",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't rain on my ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "chew",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't bite off more than you can ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "worry",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't _____, be happy"
  }, {
    "answer": "one basket",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't put all your eggs in ___ ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "boat",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't rock the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "molehill",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't make mountain out of a ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "mouth",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't look a gift horse in the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "game",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't hate the playa, hate the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "day job",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't quit your ___ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "angry",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't go to bed _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "horse",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't put the cart before the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "both ends",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't burn the candle at ____ ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "gun fight",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't bring a knife to a ___ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "small stuff",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't sweat the _____ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Labor Day",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't wear white after _____ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "bath water",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't throw the baby out with the ____ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "wind",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't spit into the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "thirty",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't trust anyone over ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "after bad",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't throw good money _____ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "wooden",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't take any ______ nickels"
  }, {
    "answer": "lily",
    "category": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
    "question": "Don't gild the ____"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Don't Cliches Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/dont-cliches-quiz.php"
}